Good morning. I think it's important to provide some context to what's going on globally while
the United States does what it always does, which is be completely self-involved in matters that are
actually not important to the rest of the world, i.e. arguing over whether or not to eulogize
somebody who aspired for the actual discrimination, death, and denigration of others. I digress.
So while this nation has been caught up in that, Israel started a whole other beef with Qatar.
Israel is inexplicably tied to the United States. Qatar just gave a whole plane to the president of
the United States. Qatar was the country that was carrying out the negotiations between H Group and
Israel. And now Israel is bombing Qatar. So this is yet another advancement of their military
onslaught in the region. At the same time this is happening, remember that boat in Venezuela that
Pete Hegseth said they had to take out because it was bringing fentanyl to the United States?
Nobody on that boat was a drug dealer. Everybody on that boat was a fisherman.
And the United States took their lives for political reasons. That means the United States
is looking to start wars in both the Western Hemisphere and using our colony in the Eastern
Hemisphere. One of our allies, France, just kicked out its fifth prime minister because they don't have
no money and they can't figure it out without taxing the rich. Meanwhile, here on U.S. soil,
while everybody's been in a kerfuffle over a... Meanwhile, a judge just ruled that 400,000 people
will lose their legal status. So they are now criminal immigrants in a country that they've been legal
immigrants in for the last how many years? They also ruled 51 to 49 not to release the Epstein files
with only two Republicans, Rand Paul and Josh Hawley, voting on the side of Democrats. And they are
proposing to take the visas of anyone who was not speaking favorably about this man who was just
unalived. And a representative of Florida just brought to the floor of Congress that they should
be able to revoke the passports of anyone speaking unfavorably about Israel. Passports, as in
U.S. citizens. So just wanted to catch you all up on that because I know that we've all been caught up
on the wrong s***. Can anything be done to stop any of this? Not that I can think of, but you can be
prepared because war is coming. In addition, the expansion of your awareness makes you harder to
manipulate.